I always come and try to put on my
yo siempre vengo y les intento poner mi
best face. I think it's been a long time,
mejor cara yo creo que hace mucho de
honestly, I haven't shown myself in a
verdad no me muestro de una manera
vulnerable way to you all. You know
vulnerable ante ustedes ustedes saben
that I'm a person who has a thousand
que yo soy una persona que tiene mil de
feelings, like I'm very sensitive and
sentimientos como que soy muy sensible y
usually I pretend that you see me
por lo general dejo como que sí me vean
when I'm down, when I'm sad and
cuando estoy mal cuando estoy triste y
all that, but it's been like many
todo eso pero han sido como muchas
stages because suddenly Juan loses 3
etapas por qué de repente Juan pierde 3
kg, takes off his cap and grows a beard
kg se quita la gorra y se deja la barba
and wow. He's great, he's on his [ __ ]
y wow Está buenísimo está en su
Prime, how good it has been for him, tse, on top of that, is it
Prime qué bien le ha venido tse encima
you? Isn't Ari prettier
está ti acaso Ari no está más guapa
since she's single? She's not
desde que está soltera también no está
on her [ __ ] Prime either. I've also put on
en su Prime también les he puesto
my best face, I've shown you that I'm
mi mejor cara les he enseñado que estoy
smiling, that I'm happy, but
sonriente que estoy feliz pero pues
really, there's like a lot going on, I
realmente hay como mucho sucediendo no
'm not this person all the time. I
soy esta persona todo el tiempo también
've also seen how they've wanted to
he visto como que me han querido
drag me into controversies lately and Ah.
embarrar en polémicas últimamente y Ah
Keep liar, of course. Here she is already
Sigue mentirosa claro Aquí ya está
saying, they've wanted to drag me into
diciendo me han querido embarrar en
controversies, no. I mean, she's going to deny
polémicas no O sea va a volver a negar
the likes we talked about again.
los lik de los que hablamos